couponswift.com 2019-05-22

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Statement**

CouponSwift.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our offerings. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. This Privacy Statement only covers the site CouponSwift.com.

 **Personal Data**

Only a user’s email address is collected when users provide registration to CouponSwift.com. By registering, you agree that CouponSwift.com may send you periodical emails promoting coupons and specials from the CouponSwift.com merchant base that may be of interest to you. Email addresses are never shared or sold to third-party marketers or third-party agencies.

 **Aggregated Information**

Aggregated information, such as which page users access or visit, and information volunteered by users is collected through various methods. For example, CouponSwift.com collects IP addresses; an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web. Web servers (the computers that “serve up” Web pages) automatically identify your computer by its IP address; when you request a page from CouponSwift.com, our servers log your IP address.

CouponSwift.com only uses IP addresses for the purposes of Web traffic analysis and trends.

 **Use of Cookies**

CouponSwift.com uses cookies for this site. A cookie is a small data file that most major websites write to your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies allow CouponSwift.com to measure activity on the site and to improve your user experience, for example by remembering your passwords and viewing preferences.

 **Children and Privacy**

CouponSwift.com encourages parents and guardians to spend time with their children online, and to be fully familiar with the sites visited by their children.

Individuals under 13  
No information should be submitted to or posted on CouponSwift.com by users under the age of 13 years without consent of their parent or guardian. CouponSwift.com does not provide any personally-identifying information for users under the age of 13, regardless of its source, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever unless disclosed during collection.

 **Newsletter & Coupon Alert**

CouponSwift.com sends newsletter or coupon alert based on your needs. Newsletter is periodical emails with promoting coupons from CouponSwift.com merchant, regularly once a week. Coupon Alert is a periodically emails with promoting informants of merchants or products you subscribed.  
Once successfully registering means you accept our privacy policy. CouponSwift.com may send you coupon alert and newsletter. Besides, if you want to opt out, just click “Unsubscribe Here” at the bottom of newsletter or coupon alert.

 **Links to Other Sites**

CouponSwift.com contains links to sites other than CouponSwift.com; those sites may not follow the same privacy policies as CouponSwift.com.

 **Effect of Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or legal rights in or on behalf of any party. We may update this privacy policy to this page, and we encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information about our privacy practices.

 **Contact Us**

Please contact us if you have any questions or comments about our privacy policy. You can reach us via following address: support@couponswift.com

USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR CONSENT TO THIS ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY AND THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE.
